THIERRY DEKELVER

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

PROFILE

My journey in IT started with SatCom, BlueForceTracking and Comms in the military. Later I developed more skills in building and implementing field network kits for the NGO MSF. Good teamwork and communication skills were of vital importance in these previous work experiences. And now, I want to go deeper into programming, as a web developer. I am very motivated to constantly develop my skills and grow professionally. I am confident in my ability to come up with interesting ideas and work in team on existing projects.

SOME DEPLOYED SAMPLES

MERN, MongoDB, Express, React.js, Node.js: https://phoenixplanner-youplan.firebaseapp.com
React.js, Redux, Firebase: https://phoenixplanner-youplan.firebaseapp.com
Angular, NgRx, Firebase: https://phoenixrecipebook.web.app
Vue.js, Firebase, CRUD: https://phoenixsmoothies-yousmoothie.web.app
Vue.js, Firebase, Coogle GeoLocation: https://phoenixgeo-yougeo.web.app
Vanilla JavaScript, Tetris retro game: https://phoenixtetris.netlify.app

FAVORITE PROJECTS

Food additives project: React.js, Redux, Tesseract.js, PostgreSQL, Node.js, (used Docker as VM): https://github.com/Jitgitbit/whatez-server | https://github.com/Jitgitbit/whatez-client Blockchain project: Python, Vue.js, (used Anaconda as VM): https://github.com/Jitgitbit/python-exercise-one

EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER GRADUATE

Codaisseur | Jan 2020 - March 2020

Intensive 11 weeks bootcamp for full stack web development in JavaScript, React, Redux, Git, Github, React Native, SQL, Docker, PG, etc...

MOBILE FIELD IMPLEMENTATION OFFICER

MSF | March 2016 - Dec 2019

Implementing entire IT setup for MSF missions and projects, IT-infrastructure, NAS, security and internet connectivity. Piloting new technologies for less expensive internet connectivity in remote areas. Reducing cost often by more than 50%.

MILITARY INFANTRY NEC SPECIALIST

ABL | March 2006 - March 2016

Providing and maintaining Network and Communication capability of NATO operations in base and combat situations. Working on individual independent basis, in teams, and as team leader.

EDUCATION

THE OUTSTANDING CODAISSEUR BOOTCAMP

Codaisseur | Jan 2020 - March 2020

This very intensive web dev training brought me the skills in record time to build powerful apps with the technologies described above.

I also learned here how to professionally collaborate in team on Git for working on projects. And I'm eager to learn much more.

NCO LEVEL MILITARY EDUCATION FOR NEC SPECIALIST

Royal Belgian Military Academy | 2007 - 2015

Education in the military is spread out over longer periods because we have intervals of missions, which are prioritised. On average 5 months of education, 6 months mission/s, 1 month leave per year.

VIDEO DEMO LINKS

Samples demo:

https://www.loom.com/share/a092c cbd6b9b490891474fa4d509cd3a

WhatEz demo:

https://www.loom.com/share/950a0 bd8728449b3b44a4e99c95925d5

CONTACT

thierry.dekelver@gmail.com +32486118464 https://github.com/Jitgitbit https://www.linkedin.com/in/thierr ydekelver https://thierryd.netlify.com

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

GITHUB:

https://github.com/Jitgitbit

Programming:

JavaScript | TypeScript | Python |
React.js | Vue.js | Angular | React
Native | Redux | Json SSE | Git |
Github | Node.js | Express.js | Axios
| CORS | Sequelize | Bcrypt | JWT |
HTML | CSS | Tesseract.js | Multer |
REST API | Firebase, NoSQL | SQL |
Docker | PostgresQL | RegEx

Natural languages:

Dutch, English, French (learning Spanish)

PERSONAL SKILLS

Creative spirit
Reliable and professional
Organized
Time management
Team player
Fast and eager learner
Motivated

HOBBIES

football (soccer) table tennis learning more programming languages and technologies